[
      {
            "question": "3 + 2",
            "answer": 5
      },
      {
            "question": "4 + 8",
            "answer": 12
      },
      {
            "question": "4 * 8",
            "answer": 32
      },
      {
            "question": "8 / 4",
            "answer": 2
      },
      {
            "question": "7 ^ 2",
            "answer": 49
      },
      {
            "question": "4 ^ 2",
            "answer": 16
      },
      {
            "question": "8 / 2",
            "answer": 4
      },
      {
            "question": "4 ^ 3",
            "answer": 64
      },
      {
            "question": "7 ^ 2",
            "answer": 49
      },
      {
            "question": "2 * 2",
            "answer": 4
      },
      {
            "question": "9 ^ 3",
            "answer": 729
      },
      {
            "question": "Answer to the Ultimate Question of Life, the Universe, and Everything",
            "answer": 42
      }
]